<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hobo News Network</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hobo News Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 11/28</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-11-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-11-28/</guid>
      <description>The Last SurvivorsOnly the strongest (and cunt) remainAlready in:
HobosGelatoNo KapIn control for the final spot:
Team Hide and Zeke: All Hide and Zeke needs to do is win.
Needs help:
Catch %: Win + Hide and Zeke loss + Sarah loss. Also needs to maintain point differential lead over Cunt, or have Cunt lose. Cunt: Win + Hide and Zeke loss + Sarah loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 11/21</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-11-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-11-21/</guid>
      <description>A Brief Playoff Updategotta go fast In control of their destiny 
HyperhobosGelatoNo KapOne more win by the Hobos and they lock up the Try Hard division; along with a playoff spot. Gelato and No Kap don’t have as big of a cushion as the Hobos, but there’s no threat to their playoff security if they win the last two games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 11/14</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-11-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-11-14/</guid>
      <description>Hardly Trying Division Relagated to Tebow’s Pre-Teen Fantasy Football LeagueThis division sucksNot a single team in the hardly trying division won a game this past week. NOT ONE.
Around the HoboKalen Ballage taking over the Chargers starting job?Congrats to Best Loser for being the first team to drop from #1 to #12 in ESPN’s projections over the course of a season8 teams have 4-5 wins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 11/7</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-11-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-11-7/</guid>
      <description>Trade Review Time!Trades can make or break a seasonAs we near the end of the season, it is time to look back at some of the biggest trades of the season and see which teams came out on top. Shipping out the Browns Macho Mel trades: A.J. Brown, Marquise Brown LeGarrette Cunt trades: Leonard Fournette, Julio Jones For a while it looked like Cunt really got away with a steal, but recent events have tipped the needle firmly in Mel’s favor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 10/31</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-10-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-10-31/</guid>
      <description>Schedule AnalysisBrought to you by theffhub.comKey TakeawaysThe Hobo’s schedule is perfect, but only for the Hobo’s
The Hyperhobo’s currently have a 6-1 record. If the Hyperhobo’s had to go against anyone else’s schedule up to this point in the season, their best possible record would 5-2 with either Hide and Zeke’s or Sarah’s schedule. That may make it seem like the Hobo’s have an easy schedule, but consider this: if every team had the Hyperhobo’s schedule, only Gelato #41 would match the Hobo’s 6-1 record.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 10/24</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-10-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-10-24/</guid>
      <description>Current Playoff Picture Halfway Through The SeasonBasically Everyone but the Hobos SucksDivision Leaders:
Gelato #51 - The unquestioned rulers of the Hardly Trying Division, Gelato is currently cruising to a division title. Thanks to their week 1 victory over Belchers Pistol Offense, Gelato effectively has a 2 game lead over Belcher. Gelato also has a tiebreaker win over No Kap, giving Gelato a 3 game cushion against them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 10/17</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-10-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-10-17/</guid>
      <description>Team Striegel and LeGarrette Cunt Researching Fusion TechniquesThe resulting team likely won’t be much better thoughBanished to the depths of the Hardly Division, Team Striegel and LeGarrette Cunt live a miserable existence. Starved for a victory, constantly faced with hardship and dissapointment, both teams strive for an easy way out. Enter, Fusion. Team Striegel and LeGarrette Cunt are hoping to combine their franchises into a single superteam somewhat average team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 10/10</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-10-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-10-10/</guid>
      <description>Insurmountable Lead?The Hobos may be as out of reach as the tallest peaks of EverestWhile the Hardly Trying division is closely contested, the race for the Try Hard crown may already be over. The Hobolopolis Hyperhobos have raced to a minimum 2 game lead over all other teams in the division and by far look like the best team in the division. While they have been prepping for the playoffs stockpiling talent like James Robinson, Christian McCaffery, and future WR1 Sterling Shepard, the rest of the division has been floundering in mediocrity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly hobo 10/3</title>
      <link>/post/thee-weekly-hobo-10-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/thee-weekly-hobo-10-3/</guid>
      <description>The First Souls Have Been ClaimedCorona is devasting teams around the leagueA serious case of contagious alcoholism is spreading like wildfire across Ray Rice’s Left Hook. Several teams have already felt the effects and will now go into week 4 missing several key players due to massive hangovers. We managed to get commissioner Jose’s thoughts on the matter. “He got me,” Jose said over corona spreading across the league.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 9/26</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-9-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-9-26/</guid>
      <description>There’s a new sheriff in townAnd his name is Mike GesickiIf someone were to ask you who the number one tight end in fantasy was, what would you say? Travis Kelce? George Kittle? The ghost of Rob Gronkowski? If your response would be any of those, you would be incorrect. Horribly incorrect. As of this very moment the #1 tight end according to total fantasy points is none other than Mike “The God” Gesicki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 9/19</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-9-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-9-19/</guid>
      <description>Let the Floodgates OpenAnd let the trades rush forth. Early in the morning, in the dead dark of night, team Macho Mel swindled LeGarrette Cunt into giving away their best player for a pair of scrubs. Our insider sources have confirmed that Leonard Fournette and Julio Jones are now Melians, while the Browns (AJ and Marquise) have been sentenced to serve on LeGarrette Cunt. This is a very questionable trade for LeGarrette Cunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 Power Rankings</title>
      <link>/rankings/week-1-power-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rankings/week-1-power-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: The One Inch WonderThe One Inch Wonder was a catastrophic failure in their week one matchup against the Hobos. That shouldn’t come as a surprise, given the F grade they received on their draft. Where to even start with this team. To begin with, the Hobos two starting RUNNING BACKS had more receiving yards than Inch’s starting wide receivers. Kelce and Mahomey were good as expected, but everyone else was a complete disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobo Draft Guide: QB</title>
      <link>/post/hobo-draft-preview-qb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hobo-draft-preview-qb/</guid>
      <description>A Brief IntroductionWelcome to the new and improved Hobo News Network, your #1 source of unbiased Ray Rice’s Left Hook news! Check in throughout the season for draft guides, trade reviews, game previews, and much more.
The 2020-2021 RRLH draft is tentatively scheduled for Sunday September 6 (according to Commissioner Jose).Over the next couple days we will be publishing guides for each position, to ensure you are adequately prepared and ready to dominate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 1</title>
      <link>/week-1-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-1-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: The One Inch WonderThe One Inch Wonder was a catastrophic failure in their week one matchup against the Hobos. That shouldn’t come as a surprise, given the F grade they received on their draft. Where to even start with this team. To begin with, the Hobos two starting RUNNING BACKS had more receiving yards than Inch’s starting wide receivers. Kelce and Mahomey were good as expected, but everyone else was a complete disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 10</title>
      <link>/week-10-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-10-rankings/</guid>
      <description># #12: Best Loser ═ Truly the best at losing.# #11: Team Striegel ↑ 1The story of Striegel’s season. Even when most of the week goes well, they somehow find a way to lose every single time by the slimmest of margins.# #10: The One Inch Wonder ↓ 1The One Inch Wonder is technically not dead yet. A surprise upset over the floundering Gelato has kept them in the playoff hunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 11</title>
      <link>/power-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/power-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Best Loser ═ Still the best at losing.
#11: Team Striegel ↑ 1Josh Reynolds failed Striegel.
#10: The One Inch Wonder ↓ 1The One Inch Wonder had the league’s top score of the week with a dominant victory over Best Loser. Too little too late, but at least Inch can head to the consolation tournament on a high note.
#9: Macho Mel ↑ 1Mel’s tumultuous season came to a fitting end this week in a razor thin loss to Belcher’s Pistol Offense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 11</title>
      <link>/week-11-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-11-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Best Loser ═ Still the best at losing.
#11: The One Inch Wonder &amp;gt;↑ 1The One Inch Wonder is dead. No hope left. 12 total points for Michael Thomas over the course of the season and zero RB’s tends to do that.
#10: Team Striegel ↓ 1 ↑ 2Belchers brief run in the middle of a season is a distant memory. Belcher had another loss and has one of the worst RB situations in the league.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 2</title>
      <link>/week-2-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-2-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Hide and Zeke ↑ 1Hide and Zeke narrowly came out the loser in this year’s early edition of the toilet bowl. Team Hide and Zeke took a risk by starting Scotty Miller and Mike Williams, and it backfired big time. Hide and Zeke lost by a total of 7 points. If either of them had been left on the bench, and Brandin Cooks had been started instead, Team Hide and Zeke would have won with 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 2</title>
      <link>/week-3-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-3-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Hide and Zeke ↑ 1Hide and Zeke narrowly came out the loser in this year’s early edition of the toilet bowl. Team Hide and Zeke took a risk by starting Scotty Miller and Mike Williams, and it backfired big time. Hide and Zeke lost by a total of 7 points. If either of them had been left on the bench, and Brandin Cooks had been started instead, Team Hide and Zeke would have won with 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 2</title>
      <link>/week-4-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-4-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Hide and Zeke ↑ 1Hide and Zeke narrowly came out the loser in this year’s early edition of the toilet bowl. Team Hide and Zeke took a risk by starting Scotty Miller and Mike Williams, and it backfired big time. Hide and Zeke lost by a total of 7 points. If either of them had been left on the bench, and Brandin Cooks had been started instead, Team Hide and Zeke would have won with 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 2</title>
      <link>/week-5-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-5-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Hide and Zeke ↑ 1Hide and Zeke narrowly came out the loser in this year’s early edition of the toilet bowl. Team Hide and Zeke took a risk by starting Scotty Miller and Mike Williams, and it backfired big time. Hide and Zeke lost by a total of 7 points. If either of them had been left on the bench, and Brandin Cooks had been started instead, Team Hide and Zeke would have won with 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 5</title>
      <link>/week-6-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-6-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: The One Inch Wonder ↑ 1Wonder swaps spots with Cunt and returns to the bottom. The continued absence and unreliability of Michael Thomas continues to hit this team bad. It may be time for Wonder to cut their losses and dump him.
#11: LeGarrette Cunt ↓ 1Cunt gets their first win in a shocking blowout against Striegel. Perhaps this is a sign that they should start two Ram RBs every week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 6</title>
      <link>/week-7-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-7-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Striegel ↑ 3Justin Tucker deserves better.
#11: The One Inch Wonder ↓ 1 Despite several awful performances in the starting lineup, The One Inch Wonder pulled off a dominant victory over Striegel. Not everything looks good for Wonder though; Michael Thomas is once again hurt and will likely miss even more time.
#10: Best Loser (previously known as Automongol Cocker Spaniel) ↑ 2 It has not been a good week for Best Loser, once known as Moneycock Autoloser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 8</title>
      <link>/week-8-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-8-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Striegel ═ Striegel wasted a career day from Davente Adams who scored 37.5 points, a 3rd of Striegel’s total points. Streigel’s failure stemmed from the combined 7 points from Beckham, Fant, and Peterson. In addition to that, Beckham is confirmed to be out for the season with an injury. And to pile on even more, Mark Ingram and Allen Robinson are also injured and unlikely to play this Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 9</title>
      <link>/week-9-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-9-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Best Loser ↑ 3Rough week for Best Loser. Chris Carson was ruled out in a game time decision, and then literally everyone not named Rodgers or Kupp were awful. The Browns offense was completely shutdown leading to a slow day in the office for Kareem Hunt. Tyler Lockett took a backseat to Metcalf. DJ Moore never showed up to his game, and Scotty Miller never fails to disappoint expectations when placed in the starting lineup.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>