<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hobo News Network</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hobo News Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly hobo 10/3</title>
      <link>/post/thee-weekly-hobo-10-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/thee-weekly-hobo-10-3/</guid>
      <description>The First Souls Have Been ClaimedCorona is devasting teams around the leagueA serious case of contagious alcoholism is spreading like wildfire across Ray Rice’s Left Hook. Several teams have already felt the effects and will now go into week 4 missing several key players due to massive hangovers. We managed to get commissioner Jose’s thoughts on the matter. “He got me,” Jose said over corona spreading across the league.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 9/26</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-9-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-9-26/</guid>
      <description>There’s a new sheriff in townAnd his name is Mike GesickiIf someone were to ask you who the number one tight end in fantasy was, what would you say? Travis Kelce? George Kittle? The ghost of Rob Gronkowski? If your response would be any of those, you would be incorrect. Horribly incorrect. As of this very moment the #1 tight end according to total fantasy points is none other than Mike “The God” Gesicki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weekly Hobo 9/19</title>
      <link>/post/the-weekly-hobo-9-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-weekly-hobo-9-19/</guid>
      <description>Let the Floodgates OpenAnd let the trades rush forth. Early in the morning, in the dead dark of night, team Macho Mel swindled LeGarrette Cunt into giving away their best player for a pair of scrubs. Our insider sources have confirmed that Leonard Fournette and Julio Jones are now Melians, while the Browns (AJ and Marquise) have been sentenced to serve on LeGarrette Cunt. This is a very questionable trade for LeGarrette Cunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1 Power Rankings</title>
      <link>/rankings/week-1-power-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rankings/week-1-power-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: The One Inch WonderThe One Inch Wonder was a catastrophic failure in their week one matchup against the Hobos. That shouldn’t come as a surprise, given the F grade they received on their draft. Where to even start with this team. To begin with, the Hobos two starting RUNNING BACKS had more receiving yards than Inch’s starting wide receivers. Kelce and Mahomey were good as expected, but everyone else was a complete disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobo Draft Guide: QB</title>
      <link>/post/hobo-draft-preview-qb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hobo-draft-preview-qb/</guid>
      <description>A Brief IntroductionWelcome to the new and improved Hobo News Network, your #1 source of unbiased Ray Rice’s Left Hook news! Check in throughout the season for draft guides, trade reviews, game previews, and much more.
The 2020-2021 RRLH draft is tentatively scheduled for Sunday September 6 (according to Commissioner Jose).Over the next couple days we will be publishing guides for each position, to ensure you are adequately prepared and ready to dominate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 1</title>
      <link>/week-1-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-1-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: The One Inch WonderThe One Inch Wonder was a catastrophic failure in their week one matchup against the Hobos. That shouldn’t come as a surprise, given the F grade they received on their draft. Where to even start with this team. To begin with, the Hobos two starting RUNNING BACKS had more receiving yards than Inch’s starting wide receivers. Kelce and Mahomey were good as expected, but everyone else was a complete disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 2</title>
      <link>/week-2-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-2-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Hide and Zeke ↑ 1Hide and Zeke narrowly came out the loser in this year’s early edition of the toilet bowl. Team Hide and Zeke took a risk by starting Scotty Miller and Mike Williams, and it backfired big time. Hide and Zeke lost by a total of 7 points. If either of them had been left on the bench, and Brandin Cooks had been started instead, Team Hide and Zeke would have won with 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 2</title>
      <link>/week-3-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-3-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Hide and Zeke ↑ 1Hide and Zeke narrowly came out the loser in this year’s early edition of the toilet bowl. Team Hide and Zeke took a risk by starting Scotty Miller and Mike Williams, and it backfired big time. Hide and Zeke lost by a total of 7 points. If either of them had been left on the bench, and Brandin Cooks had been started instead, Team Hide and Zeke would have won with 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 2</title>
      <link>/week-4-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/week-4-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: Team Hide and Zeke ↑ 1Hide and Zeke narrowly came out the loser in this year’s early edition of the toilet bowl. Team Hide and Zeke took a risk by starting Scotty Miller and Mike Williams, and it backfired big time. Hide and Zeke lost by a total of 7 points. If either of them had been left on the bench, and Brandin Cooks had been started instead, Team Hide and Zeke would have won with 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Rankings Week 4</title>
      <link>/power-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/power-rankings/</guid>
      <description>#12: LeGarrette Cunt ↑ 1Cunt may be winless, and they may have just put up the season’s lowest score of the week, and Ekeler may be out for the foreseeable future, but that doesn’t mean LeGarrette Cunt has to lose hope! Any day know Gronk may find a time machine and become ten years younger! And who knows, maybe Sammy Watkins will finally have his breakout season! Cunt needs to stay positive and believe that they can win at least one game this season.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>